# Nate Denys

(650) 922-0740
BELMONT, CA
NATE\_DENYS@YAHOO.COM
NATEDENYS.COM
LINKEDIN.COM/IN/NATE-DENYS
GITHUB.COM/NDENYS650

Progressive background in UI/UX practices and techniques with HTML, CSS, JS, and React. 6+ years of experience in sensitive, small business work-ethics, and fast-paced environments.

Costumer oriented team player focused on business growth and development. Adaptable Office Administrator specialized in Aviation Insurance with a B.S. in Business Economics.

## **EDUCATION**

CODIFY ACADEMY
Front-End Web Development | 2017

UC IRVINE
Business Economics | 2015

### **EXPERIENCE**

FRONT END DEVELOPER | San Francisco, CA | 2016 to 2017

- Utilized API's to create numerous dynamic applications with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ¡Query, React, and React Native
- Pushed to Github with GIT version control to work with developers remotely
- → Sketch conversions into working HTML, CSS, and JS
- Creating and developing full MERN and MEAN stack apps

#### OFFICE ADMINISTRATOR | San Carlos, CA | 2015 to 2017

- Managed and debugged the small business website
- Sped up the development process for creating Pleasure & Business renewals and invoices
- Received client and business information and created prospective documents for underwriters to quote
- → As part of a small team, increased customer account retention, averaging 5+ accounts per month
- Reconciled and reported customer renewal information during meetings

#### SECTION LEADER | Hillsdale, CA | 2010 to 2017

- Oversaw the opening of the alcohol section, memorizing all products, and writing section orders
- Anticipated weekend rushes and increased average product sales by
   5%

## **SKILLS**

HTML5	JavaScript	UI/UX	MongoDB
CSS3	ES6	Sketch	Git/Github
SASS/LESS	jQuery	React	RESTful API's
Bootstrap	JSON	Node	ARKit